-To start your own company.
But Anton Tyulenev thought differently.
He didn't listen.
Instead he stood at a whiteboard-
-And showed what he had been thinking about.
"What are you thinking about this?"
He triggered me so I started sketching on how to do it.
So he looked at me: "You can't stop."
Then followed a couple of months of persuasion on his part.
"Shit in everything that has been and everyone else," he told me.
"We're doing this."
"You and I do this. We are two of the most competent in our respective areas"-
-"Who the hell can beat us? We're doing this."
It had been in 2015 before the company Aveiono founded-
-A Lars Kristensson and Anton Tyulenev in Malmö.